<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".Home.Fragments.Account.PrivacyPolicyFragment">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_margin="@dimen/section_margin"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:drawablePadding="@dimen/view_padding"
            android:text="This Privacy Policy applies to the Arraykart Android Application "
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            app:drawableStartCompat="@drawable/ic_outline_privacy_and_policy_24" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Privacy Policy   \n============== \n \nLast updated: June 02, 2022 \n \nThis Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, \nuse and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You \nabout Your privacy rights and how the law protects You. \n \nWe use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the \nService, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with \nthis Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy has been created with the help of the \n[Privacy Policy Generator](https://www.privacypolicies.com/privacy-policy- \ngenerator/). \n \nInterpretation and Definitions   \n============================== \n \nInterpretation   \n-------------- \n \nThe words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined \nunder the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same \nmeaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural. \n \nDefinitions   \n----------- \n \nFor the purposes of this Privacy Policy: \n \n  * Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or \n    parts of our Service. \n \n  * Affiliate means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under \n    common control with a party, where &quot;control&quot; means ownership of 50% or \n    more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote \n    for election of directors or other managing authority. \n \n  * Application means the software program provided by the Company downloaded \n    by You on any electronic device, named ARRAYKART \n \n  * Company (referred to as either &quot;the Company&quot;, &quot;We&quot;, &quot;Us&quot; or &quot;Our&quot; in this \n    Agreement) refers to Arraykart Techable Private Limited, PLOT B-133 UG/ F \n    KHASRA NO 18/20 BLK, NANHEY PARK UTTAM NAGAR, DELHI, New Delhi, Delhi, \n    India, 110059. \n \n  * Country refers to: Delhi, India \n \n  * Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a \n    cellphone or a digital tablet. \n \n  * Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or \n    identifiable individual. \n \n  * Service refers to the Application. \n \n  * Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data \n    on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or \n    individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide \n    the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the \n    Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used. \n \n  * Third-party Social Media Service refers to any website or any social \n    network website through which a User can log in or create an account to \n    use the Service. \n \n  * Usage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the \n    use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, \n    the duration of a page visit). \n \n  * You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, \n    or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or \n    using the Service, as applicable. \n \n \nCollecting and Using Your Personal Data   \n======================================= \n \nTypes of Data Collected   \n----------------------- \n \nPersonal Data   \n~~~~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nWhile using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally \nidentifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. \nPersonally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: \n \n  * Email address \n \n  * First name and last name \n \n  * Phone number \n \n  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City \n \n  * Usage Data \n \n \nUsage Data   \n~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nUsage Data is collected automatically when using the Service. \n \nUsage Data may include information such as Your Device's Internet Protocol \naddress (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our \nService that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on \nthose pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. \n \nWhen You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect \ncertain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of \nmobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your \nmobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet \nbrowser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. \n \nWe may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our \nService or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device. \n \nInformation from Third-Party Social Media Services   \n~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nThe Company allows You to create an account and log in to use the Service \nthrough the following Third-party Social Media Services: \n \n  * Google \n  * Facebook \n  * Twitter \n  * LinkedIn \n \nIf You decide to register through or otherwise grant us access to a Third- \nParty Social Media Service, We may collect Personal data that is already \nassociated with Your Third-Party Social Media Service's account, such as Your \nname, Your email address, Your activities or Your contact list associated with \nthat account. \n \nYou may also have the option of sharing additional information with the \nCompany through Your Third-Party Social Media Service's account. If You choose \nto provide such information and Personal Data, during registration or \notherwise, You are giving the Company permission to use, share, and store it \nin a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. \n \nInformation Collected while Using the Application   \n~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nWhile using Our Application, in order to provide features of Our Application, \nWe may collect, with Your prior permission: \n \n  * Information regarding your location \n \n  * Pictures and other information from your Device's camera and photo library \n \n \nWe use this information to provide features of Our Service, to improve and \ncustomize Our Service. The information may be uploaded to the Company's \nservers and/or a Service Provider's server or it may be simply stored on Your \ndevice. \n \nYou can enable or disable access to this information at any time, through Your \nDevice settings. \n \nUse of Your Personal Data   \n------------------------- \n \nThe Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes: \n \n  * To provide and maintain our Service , including to monitor the usage of \n    our Service. \n \n  * To manage Your Account: to manage Your registration as a user of the \n    Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different \n    functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered \n    user. \n \n  * For the performance of a contract: the development, compliance and \n    undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services \n    You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service. \n \n  * To contact You: To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other \n    equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile \n    application's push notifications regarding updates or informative \n    communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted \n    services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for \n    their implementation. \n \n  * To provide You with news, special offers and general information about \n    other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those \n    that you have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted \n    not to receive such information. \n \n  * To manage Your requests: To attend and manage Your requests to Us. \n \n  * For business transfers: We may use Your information to evaluate or conduct \n    a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or \n    other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going \n    concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in \n    which Personal Data held by Us about our Service users is among the assets \n    transferred. \n \n  * For other purposes : We may use Your information for other purposes, such \n    as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness \n    of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Service, \n    products, services, marketing and your experience. \n \n \nWe may share Your personal information in the following situations: \n \n  * With Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with \n    Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to \n    contact You. \n  * For business transfers: We may share or transfer Your personal information \n    in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company \n    assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our business to \n    another company. \n  * With Affiliates: We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in \n    which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. \n    Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint \n    venture partners or other companies that We control or that are under \n    common control with Us. \n  * With business partners: We may share Your information with Our business \n    partners to offer You certain products, services or promotions. \n  * With other users: when You share personal information or otherwise \n    interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be \n    viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside. If You \n    interact with other users or register through a Third-Party Social Media \n    Service, Your contacts on the Third-Party Social Media Service may see \n    Your name, profile, pictures and description of Your activity. Similarly, \n    other users will be able to view descriptions of Your activity, \n    communicate with You and view Your profile. \n  * With Your consent : We may disclose Your personal information for any \n    other purpose with Your consent. \n \nRetention of Your Personal Data   \n------------------------------- \n \nThe Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary \nfor the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your \nPersonal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations \n(for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable \nlaws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. \n \nThe Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage \nData is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data \nis used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our \nService, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time \nperiods. \n \nTransfer of Your Personal Data   \n------------------------------ \n \nYour information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company's \noperating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the \nprocessing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — \nand maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country \nor other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ \nthan those from Your jurisdiction. \n \nYour consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such \ninformation represents Your agreement to that transfer. \n \nThe Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data \nis treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer \nof Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless \nthere are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and \nother personal information. \n \nDisclosure of Your Personal Data   \n-------------------------------- \n \nBusiness Transactions   \n~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nIf the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, Your \nPersonal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your Personal \nData is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. \n \nLaw enforcement   \n~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nUnder certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your \nPersonal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by \npublic authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency). \n \nOther legal requirements   \n~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ \n \nThe Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such \naction is necessary to: \n \n  * Comply with a legal obligation \n  * Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company \n  * Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service \n  * Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public \n  * Protect against legal liability \n \nSecurity of Your Personal Data   \n------------------------------ \n \nThe security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no \nmethod of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is \n100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect \nYour Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security. \n \nChildren's Privacy   \n================== \n \nOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly \ncollect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. \nIf You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided \nUs with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have \ncollected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification \nof parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our \nservers. \n \nIf We need to rely on consent as a legal basis for processing Your information \nand Your country requires consent from a parent, We may require Your parent's \nconsent before We collect and use that information. \n \nLinks to Other Websites   \n======================= \n \nOur Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. \nIf You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party's \nsite. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You \nvisit. \n \nWe have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy \npolicies or practices of any third party sites or services. \n \nChanges to this Privacy Policy   \n============================== \n \nWe may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any \nchanges by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. \n \nWe will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior \nto the change becoming effective and update the &quot;Last updated&quot; date at the top \nof this Privacy Policy. \n \nYou are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. \nChanges to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this \npage. \n \nContact Us   \n========== \n \nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us: \n \n  * By email: yourfriends@arraykart.com \n \n  * By visiting this page on our website: https://arraykart.com/ \n \n  * By phone number: +919311900912 \n \n \n"
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/text" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Arraykart App is a property of Arraykart Techable Private Limited, an Indian Company registered under the  Companies Act, 2013 having its registered office at B-133 UGF, Nanhey Park, Uttam Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi - 110  059."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Contact information. We might collect your name, email, mobile number, phone number, street, city, state, Pincode,  country, and IP address"
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Payment and billing information. We might collect your billing name, billing address and payment method when  you buy a ticket. We NEVER collect your credit card number or credit card expiry date or other details pertaining to  your credit card on our Application. Credit card information will be obtained and processed by our online payment  partner CC Avenue."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Information you post. We collect the information you post in a public space on our Application or on a third-party  social media Application belonging to Arraykart."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Demographic information. We may collect demographic information about you, events you like, events you intend  to participate in, tickets you buy, or any other information provided by you during the use of our Application. We might  collect this as a part of a survey also."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Other information. If you use our Application, we may collect information about your IP address and the browser  you're using. We might look at what Application you came from, duration of time spent on our Application, pages  accessed or what Application you visit when you leave us. We might also collect the type of mobile device you are  using, or the version of the operating system your computer or device is running."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We collect information in different ways"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We collect information directly from you. We collect information directly from you when you register for an event  or buy tickets. We also collect information if you post a comment on our Applications or ask us a question through  phone or email."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We collect information from you passively. We use tracking tools like Google Analytics, Google Webmaster, browser cookies and web beacons for collecting information about your usage of our Application."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We get information about you from third parties. For akfrontend, if you use an integrated social media feature on  our Applications. The third-party social media Application will give us certain information about you. This could  include your name and email address. "
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Use of your personal information "
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information to contact you: We might use the information you provide to contact you for confirmation of a  purchase on our Application or for other promotional purposes."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information to respond to your requests or questions. We might use your information to confirm your  registration for an event or contest."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information to improve our products and services. We might use your information to customize your  experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information to look at Application trends and customer interests. We may use your information to make  our Application and products better. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get  from third parties."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our  Applications. "
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information for marketing purposes. We might send you information about special promotions or offers.  We might also tell you about new features or products. These might be our own offers or products, or third-party  offers or products we think you might find interesting. Or, for akfrontend, if you buy tickets from us we'll enroll you in our  newsletter."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information to send you transactional communications. We might send you emails or SMS about your  account or a ticket purchase."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We use information as otherwise permitted by law."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Sharing of information with third-parties"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. We share information with  vendors who help us manage our online registration process or payment processors or transactional message  processors. Some vendors may be located outside of India. "
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We will share information with the event organizers. We share your information with event organizers and other  parties responsible for fulfilling the purchase obligation. The event organizers and other parties may use the  information we give them as described in their privacy policies."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We will share information with our business partners. This includes a third party who provide or sponsor an  event, or who operates a venue where we hold events. Our partners use the information we give them as described  in their privacy policies."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. We  will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or  investigatory body requests. Or, we might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business. For akfrontend, if part of our  business is sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="We may share your information for reasons not described in this policy. We will tell you before we do this."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Email Opt-Out"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. To stop receiving our promotional emails, please email  unsubscriber@arraykart.com. It may take about ten days to process your request. Even if you opt out of getting  marketing messages, we will still be sending you transactional messages through email and SMS about your  purchases."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Third party Applications"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="If you click on one of the links to third party Applications, you may be taken to Applications we do not control. This  policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those Applications. Read the privacy policy of other Applications  carefully. We are not responsible for these third-party Applications."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Updates to this policy"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="This Privacy Policy was last updated on 28.02.2022. From time to time we may change our privacy practices. We will  notify you of any material changes to this policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our  Application. Please check our Application periodically for updates."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="Jurisdiction"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="If you choose to visit the Application, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the  Application's terms of use. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the  laws of India."
            android:textColor="@color/text"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/view_bottom_margin"
            android:text="If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, you can also email us at  yourfriends@arraykart.com"
            android:textColor="@color/heading"
            android:textSize="@dimen/sub_heading"
            android:visibility="gone" />

    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>